Guide to the United Federation of Teachers Records WAG.022
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III: Officers and Staff Files
  - Subseries III:F: Sandra Feldman Files.
    - Mitchell, Elaine: Correspondence, 1970 (Box 154, Folder 15)
    - Mobilization for Youth, 1966-1967 (Box 154, Folder 16)
    - Model Cities Program, 1966-1967 (Box 154, Folder 17)
    - Morse, Wayne: Senator, 1973 (Box 154, Folder 18)
    - National Education Association, 1972-1976 (Box 154, Folder 19)
    - New York City Budget Crisis, 1971 (Box 154, Folder 20)
    - New York City Budget Crisis, 1975 (Box 154, Folder 21)
    - New York Urban Coalition Education Task Force, 1967-1972 (Box 154, Folder 22)
    - Open Corridor Program, 1970 (Box 154, Folder 23)
    - O'Reilly, Peter: Father O'Reilly Defense Committee, 1968 (Box 154, Folder 24)
    - Paraprofessionals, Mar 1967-Apr 1968 (Box 155, Folder 1)
    - Paraprofessionals, May 1968-Jul 1968 (Box 155, Folder 2)
    - Paraprofessionals, Apr 1969-Jul 1971 (Box 155, Folder 3)
    - Paraprofessionals, Aug 1971-Oct 1974 (Box 155, Folder 4)
    - Paraprofessionals: Collective Bargaining/Contract, 1972 (Box 155, Folder 5)
    - Paraprofessionals: Organizing, 1969, 1971-1972 (Box 155, Folder 6)
    - Paraprofessionals: Project on Developing Alternative Qualifications and Credentials for Paraprofessionals, Feb 11, 1971 (Box 155, Folder 7)
    - Parent Complaint Board, 1968-1969 (Box 155, Folder 8)
    - Parents Association, 1965-1970 (Box 155, Folder 9)
    - Parents Council: District 2, 1967 (Box 155, Folder 10)
    - Parents Resisting Invasion of Rights in Training of Youth (PRIORITY), 1971 (Box 155, Folder 11)
    - Parents Review Board, 1969 (Box 155, Folder 12)
    - Pension, 1972 (Box 155, Folder 13)
    - Pension, 1973 (Box 155, Folder 14)
    - Pension, 1975-1976 (Box 155, Folder 15)
    - Pension: Handbook, undated (Box 155, Folder 16)
    - People against Racism in Education, 1975-1976 (Box 155, Folder 17)
    - Performance Contracting, 1970 (Box 155, Folder 18)
    - Performance Contracting, 1971-1975 (Box 155, Folder 19)
    - Personnel Committee: Report, 1962-1963, 1968 (Box 155, Folder 20)
    - Poor People's Campaign, 1965-1968 (Box 155, Folder 21)
    - Press Releases, 1965-1969, 1973, 1975 (Box 155, Folder 22)
    - Prideaux, Ric, 1966 (Box 155, Folder 23)
    - Probitsky, Burke, 1964, 1968 (Box 155, Folder 24)
    - Procaccino, Mario: Comptroller, 1965-1969 (Box 155, Folder 25)
    - Public Education and Religious Liberty (PEARL), 1967-1970 (Box 155, Folder 26)
    - PEARL, 1971 (Box 155, Folder 27)
    - Wantaugh Faculty Association: Negotiations, 1971 (Box 155, Folder 28)
    - WBAI, 99.5 FM, 1969, 1972 (Box 155, Folder 29)
  - Subseries III:G: George Fesko Files
    - 105 A, 1974-1975 (Box 156, Folder 1)
    - 105 A Candidates, 1974-1975 (Box 156, Folder 2)
    - 105 A Course, 1974-1975 (Box 156, Folder 3)
    - 105 A Hearings, 1975 (Box 156, Folder 4)
    - A and B Classes, 1975 (Box 156, Folder 5)
    - Absenteeism, 1974 (Box 156, Folder 6)
    - Accountability, 1974-1975 (Box 156, Folder 7)
    - Aquart, Jacqueline, 1977 (Box 156, Folder 8)
    - Arbitrations, 1973-1974 (Box 156, Folder 9)
    - Arbitrations, 1975 (Box 156, Folder 10)
    - Arbitration Cases, Jun 1976 (Box 156, Folder 11)
    - Arbitration Cases, Aug 1976-Nov 1976 (Box 156, Folder 12)
    - Arricale, Frank, 1975 (Box 156, Folder 13)
    - Assigned Teachers, 1971-1972 (Box 156, Folder 14)
    - Attendance Teachers, 1970-1975 (Box 156, Folder 15)
    - Attendance Teachers Elections, 1974-1976 (Box 156, Folder 16)
    - Attendance Teachers Grievances, 1964, 1974-1975 (Box 156, Folder 17)
    - Bilingual Teachers, 1970-1975 (Box 156, Folder 18)
    - Board of Education Division of Personnel, 1974 (Box 156, Folder 19)
    - Board of Education: Memos, 1961, 1969-1976 (Box 156, Folder 20)
    - Bradford, Paul, 1976 (Box 156, Folder 21)
    - Broadsheets/Newsletters, 1975-1976 (Box 156, Folder 22)
    - Cherasard, Rosny, 1976 (Box 156, Folder 23)
    - Chinitz, Freda, 1975-1976 (Box 156, Folder 24)
    - Court Cases, 1966-1976 (Box 156, Folder 25)
    - DeLeonardis, Vito, 1972 (Box 156, Folder 26)
    - District Representatives Administrative Procedures, 1968-1973 (Box 156, Folder 27)
    - District Representatives Elections, 1970-1971 (Box 156, Folder 28)
    - District Representatives Elections, 1973 (Box 156, Folder 29)
    - Division of Educational Planning, 1974 (Box 156, Folder 30)
    - Drug Abuse Program, District 27 Guidance Chapter, 1974-1975 (Box 157, Folder 1)
    - Drug Program, undated, 1974-1975 (Box 157, Folder 2)
    - Dushane Fund Reports, 1974-1975 (Box 157, Folder 3)
    - Equal Opportunity, 1974 (Box 157, Folder 4)
    - Excessed Personnel, undated, 1971 (Box 157, Folder 5)
    - Excessing and Layoffs, 1974-1975 (Box 157, Folder 6)
    - Excessing Rules, 1955, 1970-1977 (Box 157, Folder 7)
    - Executive Board, 1975-1976 (Box 157, Folder 8)
    - Guidance Counselors, 1975 (Box 157, Folder 9)
    - Levine, Abraham: Correspondence and Memoranda, 1975-1976 (Box 157, Folder 10)
    - Magidson, Herb, 1976 (Box 157, Folder 11)
    - Memoranda, 1975 (Box 157, Folder 12)
    - Memoranda, 1976 (Box 157, Folder 13)
    - Memoranda, 1977 (Box 157, Folder 14)
    - Memoranda (Sandy Feldman), 1976-1977 (Box 157, Folder 15)
    - Personnel Memos, 1978 (Box 157, Folder 16)
    - Personnel: Problems, 1976-1977 (Box 157, Folder 17)
    - Schwartz, Benjamin, 1976 (Box 157, Folder 18)
    - Simon, Bernard, 1977 (Box 157, Folder 19)
    - Stein, Leonard, 1976 (Box 157, Folder 20)
    - Steiner, Mildred, 1976 (Box 157, Folder 21)
    - Teacher Layoffs, 1975 (Box 157, Folder 22)
    - Weiss, Sydelle, 1976 (Box 157, Folder 23)
    - White, Henrietta, 1975 (Box 157, Folder 24)
    - WIN (Teachers' Association), 1972-1973 (Box 157, Folder 25)
    - WNYE, 1972 (Box 157, Folder 26)
  - Subseries III:H: Leo Hoenig Files
    - Administrative Assignments, 1966-1967 (Box 157, Folder 27)
    - Arbitration, 1983-1984 (Box 157, Folder 28)
    - Book Ban, 1971 (Box 157, Folder 29)
    - Budget, 1964 (Box 157, Folder 30)
    - Budget Crisis, 1976-1977 (Box 157, Folder 31)
    - Cafeteria Survey, 1978 (Box 157, Folder 32)
    - Chapter Chairman: Training, 1970 (Box 157, Folder 33)
    - Chapter Chair Meetings, 1977-1979 (Box 157, Folder 34)
    - Chapter Officers, undated (Box 157, Folder 35)
    - Classroom Discipline, 1975 (Box 157, Folder 36)
    - Collective Bargaining, 1961, 1963, 1967 (Box 157, Folder 37)
    - Collective Bargaining: Campaign, undated, 1962 (Box 157, Folder 38)
    - Collective Bargaining: Election Campaign, 1961-1963 (Box 157, Folder 39)
    - Committee on Political Education (COPE), 1976, 1984-1988 (Box 157, Folder 40)
    - Community School Board 25: Bylaws, 1970 (Box 158, Folder 1)
    - Conferences, 1960-1964 (Box 158, Folder 2)
    - Conferences, 1964-1969 (Box 158, Folder 3)
    - Conferences, 1970-1974 (Box 158, Folder 4)
    - Conferences, 1975-1980 (Box 158, Folder 5)
    - Contracts, 1987 (Box 158, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1974 (Box 158, Folder 7)
    - Decentralization, undated (Box 158, Folder 8)
    - Difficult/Problem Schools, 1979 (Box 158, Folder 9)
    - District 25, Queens, 1965-1971 (Box 158, Folder 10)
    - District 25, Queens, 1972-1975 (Box 158, Folder 11)
    - District 25, Queens, 1976-1978 (Box 158, Folder 12)
    - District 25, Queens, 1979-1981 (Box 158, Folder 13)
    - District 25, Queens, 1982, 1987-1988 (Box 158, Folder 14)
    - District 25, Queens: Department of Education Emergency School Aid Act (ESAA) Program, 1976-1977 (Box 158, Folder 15)
    - District 25, Queens: In Review, 1969-1973 (Box 158, Folder 16)
    - District 25, Queens: Organization, 1968 (Box 158, Folder 17)
    - District 25, Queens: Report, 1969-1971 (Box 158, Folder 18)
    - District 25, Queens: The United Teacher, 1969-1970 (Box 158, Folder 19)
    - District 25, Queens: UFT Sentinel, 1973-1974 (Box 158, Folder 20)
    - District 48, Queens, 1960-1964 (Box 158, Folder 21)
    - Education Briefs, undated (Box 158, Folder 22)
    - Federal Aid to Education, 1963-1966 (Box 158, Folder 23)
    - Grievances: General Decisions, 1976-1977 (Box 158, Folder 24)
    - Grievances: Biener, Lawrence, 1969 (Box 158, Folder 25)
    - Grievances: Cronacher, Lola, 1983, 1986 (Box 158, Folder 26)
    - Grievances: Emmanuelle, Salvatore, 1985, 1988 (Box 158, Folder 27)
    - Grievances: Glassman, Michael, 1965-1966 (Box 158, Folder 28)
    - Grievances: Green, Mary, 1962-1963 (Box 158, Folder 29)
    - Grievances: Gutkin, David, 1983-1991 (Box 158, Folder 30)
    - Grievances: Rothman, Phyllis, 1988 (Box 158, Folder 31)
    - Grievances: Satz, Ezra, 1988, 1990 (Box 158, Folder 32)
    - Grievances: Skala, Frank, 1963-1968, 1983-1984 (Box 158, Folder 33)
    - Grievances: St. Cyr, Constance, 1979-1980 (Box 158, Folder 34)
    - Grievances: St. Cyr, Constance, 1981-1987 (Box 158, Folder 35)
    - Guidance Counselors, 1973-1974 (Box 158, Folder 36)
    - Harassment, 1970-1971 (Box 158, Folder 37)
    - Health Plans, undated, 1973 (Box 158, Folder 38)
    - High Schools: Bowne HS, 1969 (Box 158, Folder 39)
    - Hoenig, Leo: Awards, 1973-1974, 1980 (Box 158, Folder 40)
    - Hoenig, Leo: Family History, 1968 (Box 158, Folder 41)
    - Hoenig, Leo: Chapter Chairman, 1969 (Box 158, Folder 42)
    - Hoenig, Leo: Membership Cards, 1972-1973, 1979-1980 (Box 158, Folder 43)
    - Human Relations Course Requirement, 1969 (Box 158, Folder 44)
    - Integration, 1963-1964, 1974, 1977 (Box 158, Folder 45)
    - Junior High School Committee, 1963-1975 (Box 158, Folder 46)
    - Junior High Schools: "Beginning Teaching", 1963 (Box 158, Folder 47)
    - Junior High Schools: Facilitators, 1988 (Box 158, Folder 48)
    - Junior High Schools: Intermediate School 61 Annex, 1976 (Box 158, Folder 49)
    - Junior High Schools: Intermediate School 201, Personnel, 1966 (Box 158, Folder 50)
    - Junior High Schools: Intermediate School 237, 1976 (Box 158, Folder 51)
    - Junior High Schools: Junior High School (JHS) 168 Parsons, 1962-1964 (Box 158, Folder 52)
    - Junior High Schools: JHS 168 Parsons, 1965 (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - Junior High Schools: JHS 168 Parsons, 1966-1967 (Box 159, Folder 2)
    - Junior High Schools: JHS 168 Parsons, 1968-1970 (Box 159, Folder 3)
    - Junior High Schools: JHS 168 Parsons, 1971-1972 (Box 159, Folder 4)
    - Junior High Schools: JHS 168 Parsons, 1973-1978 (Box 159, Folder 5)
    - Junior High Schools: JHS 168 Parsons, 1979-1982 (Box 159, Folder 6)
    - Junior High Schools: JHS 168 Parsons, 1983-1984 (Box 159, Folder 7)
    - Junior High Schools: JHS 168 Parsons, 1985-1986 (Box 159, Folder 8)
    - Junior High Schools: JHS 168 Parsons, 1987-1989 (Box 159, Folder 9)
    - Junior High Schools: JHS 168 Parsons, Chapter Memos, 1970-1978 (Box 159, Folder 10)
    - Junior High Schools: JHS 168 Parsons, General Organization, 1967, 1971 (Box 159, Folder 11)
    - Junior High Schools: JHS 168 Parsons, Legislative Action, 1970-1972 (Box 159, Folder 12)
    - Junior High Schools: JHS 168 Parsons, Legislative Memos, 1970 (Box 159, Folder 13)
    - Junior High Schools: JHS 168 Parsons, Narcotics Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 159, Folder 14)
    - Junior High Schools: JHS 168 Parsons, Parents Association, 1959-1981 (Box 159, Folder 15)
    - Junior High Schools: JHS 168 Parsons, Parents Association, Bulletin and Chronicle, 1959-1977 (Box 159, Folder 16)
    - Junior High Schools: JHS 168 Parsons, Policy Committee, 1968-1981 (Box 159, Folder 17)
    - Junior High Schools: JHS 168 Parsons, Principal's Notices, 1962-1979 (Box 159, Folder 18)
    - Junior High Schools: Restructuring, 1965, 1970 (Box 159, Folder 19)
    - Legal, undated, 1970 (Box 159, Folder 20)
    - Legislative, undated, 1967 (Box 159, Folder 21)
    - Mentor Program, 1987-1989 (Box 159, Folder 22)
    - Mid-Queens Community Council, 1967 (Box 159, Folder 23)
    - National Education Association (NEA): Annual Meeting, 1973 (Box 159, Folder 24)
    - NEA: City Teachers Association, 1962-1963 (Box 159, Folder 25)
    - NEA: New York City Educator, 1961-1962 (Box 159, Folder 26)
    - NEA: Teachers Bargaining Organization, undated, 1961 (Box 159, Folder 27)
    - New Teachers, 1965-1973, 1989 (Box 159, Folder 28)
    - Obituaries, 1971 (Box 159, Folder 29)
    - Open School Week, 1970-1971 (Box 159, Folder 30)
    - Paraprofessionals, 1973, 1979, 1988-1990 (Box 159, Folder 31)
    - Parent-Teachers Association: Homework, 1968 (Box 159, Folder 32)
    - Primary Schools: PS 200, 1967-1968 (Box 159, Folder 33)
    - Programming Section, 1965-1973 (Box 159, Folder 34)
    - Promotion Policy, 1982-1983 (Box 159, Folder 35)
    - Public Education Association, undated (Box 159, Folder 36)
    - Public Schools of New York City: Staff Bulletin, 1964, 1967 (Box 159, Folder 37)
    - Queens College: The Phoenix, 1968 (Box 159, Folder 38)
    - Report Cards, 1985 (Box 159, Folder 39)
    - Sabbatical, 1976-1978 (Box 159, Folder 40)
    - Salary, 1969-1970 (Box 159, Folder 41)
    - Salary Schedule, 1978-1980 (Box 159, Folder 42)
    - School Allotment, 1970-1974 (Box 159, Folder 43)
    - School Board: By-Laws, 1970 (Box 159, Folder 44)
    - School Board: District One, Election, 1974 (Box 159, Folder 45)
    - School Board: District 25, Election, 1970 (Box 159, Folder 46)
    - School Policies, 1966 (Box 159, Folder 47)
    - School Safety, 1980-1981 (Box 159, Folder 48)
    - Secretaries, 1964-1990 (Box 159, Folder 49)
    - Seniority, undated (Box 159, Folder 50)
    - Special Service Schools, 1963 (Box 159, Folder 51)
    - Staff Development Program, undated (Box 159, Folder 52)
    - Staff Relations, 1956, 1965 (Box 159, Folder 53)
    - Stavisky-Goodman Law, undated (Box 159, Folder 54)
    - Strike: Anti-Community Control (pro-UFT) Literature, 1968 (Box 159, Folder 55)
    - Strike: Clips, 1968 (Box 159, Folder 56)
    - Strike: Council of Supervisory Associations, 1968 (Box 159, Folder 57)
    - Strike: District 25, Anti-UFT Literature, 1968 (Box 159, Folder 58)
    - Strike: District 25, District Chairman's File, 1967 (Box 159, Folder 59)
    - Strike: District 25, District Chairman's File, 1968 (Box 159, Folder 60)
    - Strike: District 25, Handouts, 1968 (Box 159, Folder 61)
    - Strike: District 25, Strike Plans, 1975 (Box 159, Folder 62)
    - Strike: District 25, UFT Materials, 1968 (Box 159, Folder 63)
    - Strike: Information, 1967-1969, 1975 (Box 159, Folder 64)
    - Strike: Non-UFT Materials, 1967 (Box 159, Folder 65)
    - Strike: Picketing, 1962 (Box 159, Folder 66)
    - Strike: Scabs, 1968 (Box 159, Folder 67)
    - Strike: "The Untold Story of Ocean Hill", 1968 (Box 159, Folder 68)
    - Strike: UFT Literature, 1967 (Box 159, Folder 69)
    - Supervisors, 1966-1967 (Box 159, Folder 70)
    - Teacher Union Awards, 1964, 1976-1980 (Box 159, Folder 71)
    - Teacher's Freedom Party, undated (Box 159, Folder 72)
    - Time Clocks, 1987-1989 (Box 159, Folder 73)
    - Union Democracy: Spur, 1963 (Box 159, Folder 74)
    - UFT Staff Party, 1966 (Box 159, Folder 75)
    - United Action, 1962-1970 (Box 159, Folder 76)
    - Vocational High School Committee: Non-Budgetary Demands, 1967 (Box 159, Folder 77)
  - Subseries III:I: Sol Levine Files.
    - Bilingual Education, 1968, 1972-1975 (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - College Scholarship Fund, 1970-1975 (Box 160, Folder 2)
    - Community Control, 1966, 1968-1970 (Box 160, Folder 3)
    - Community Control: Harlem Liberation School, undated (Box 160, Folder 4)
    - Community Control: Ocean Hill-Brownsville, 1968 (Box 160, Folder 5)
    - Comprehensive Program for American Schools (COMPAS): More Effective Schools Program (MES), 1968-1972 (Box 160, Folder 6)
    - COMPAS: MES, 1973-1975 (Box 160, Folder 7)
    - Comprehensive and Vocational High Schools, 1966-1967 (Box 160, Folder 8)
    - Conferences, 1964-1966 (Box 160, Folder 9)
    - Conferences, 1967-1968 (Box 160, Folder 10)
    - Conferences, 1969-1970 (Box 160, Folder 11)
    - Conferences, 1971-1973 (Box 160, Folder 12)
    - Conferences: Negro History Conference, AFT, 1965-1967 (Box 160, Folder 13)
    - Continuing Education Committee, 1972-1977 (Box 160, Folder 14)
    - Contract Demands: General, 1967, 1969 (Box 160, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 1965-1973 (Box 160, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, 1974-1977 (Box 160, Folder 17)
    - Draft Deferment, 1970 (Box 160, Folder 18)
    - District Representative, 1969-1970 (Box 160, Folder 19)
    - Elections, 1963, 1965 (Box 160, Folder 20)
    - Excessing of Teachers, 1955, 1965, 1970-1974 (Box 160, Folder 21)
    - Grievances, 1962-1963 (Box 161, Folder 1)
    - Grievances, 1964 (Box 161, Folder 2)
    - Grievances, 1965 (Box 161, Folder 3)
    - Home Economics Committee, 1972-1975 (Box 161, Folder 4)
    - Industrial Arts Committee, 1964-1968 (Box 161, Folder 5)
    - Intellectually Gifted Children, 1971 (Box 161, Folder 6)
    - Junior High Schools: Adams JHS, 1969-1971 (Box 161, Folder 7)
    - Junior High Schools: Contract Demands, 1970-1971 (Box 161, Folder 8)
    - Junior High Schools: Contract Demands, 1972 (Box 161, Folder 9)
    - Junior High Schools: Contract Demands, 1974 (Box 161, Folder 10)
    - Junior High Schools: Contract Demands, 1975 (Box 161, Folder 11)
    - Junior High Schools: Restructuring, 1969-1972 (Box 161, Folder 12)
    - Labor Committee on Latin American Advancement, 1975 (Box 161, Folder 13)
    - Librarians Committee: Contract Negotiations, 1966-1974 (Box 161, Folder 14)
    - Lobenthal, Martin: Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 161, Folder 15)
    - Lobenthal, Martin: Correspondence, 1966 (Box 161, Folder 16)
    - Lobenthal, Martin: Correspondence, 1967 (Box 161, Folder 17)
    - Mass Resignations, 1962-1963, 1967 (Box 162, Folder 1)
    - More Effective Schools (MES): Joseph Alsop Articles and Clippings, 1964, 1966-1972 (Box 162, Folder 2)
    - MES: Junior High Schools, 1963, 1966-1967 (Box 162, Folder 3)
    - MES: Junior High Schools, 1969-1971 (Box 162, Folder 4)
    - MES: Schools-Space, 1963, 1968, 1972 (Box 162, Folder 5)
    - Negro Teachers Association, 1967 (Box 162, Folder 6)
    - New York-Harlem Committee on Racial Equality: "A Proposal for an Independent Board of Education for Harlem", 1967 (Box 162, Folder 7)
    - Project City Science, 1975-1977 (Box 162, Folder 8)
    - Project City Science: Reports 1-3, 1974-1975 (Box 162, Folder 9)
    - Project City Science: Reports 4-6, 1975-1976 (Box 162, Folder 10)
    - Project City Science: Reports 7, 9-10, 1976-1977 (Box 162, Folder 11)
    - Project City Science: Reports 11-13, 1977-1978 (Box 162, Folder 12)
    - Public Schools of New York City: Staff Bulletin, 1964, 1967 (Box 162, Folder 13)
    - Teachers' Representative Union, 1970-1973 (Box 162, Folder 14)
    - Welfare Benefits, 1965-1967, 1974 (Box 162, Folder 15)
    - Welfare Fund, 1966 (Box 162, Folder 16)
    - Welfare Fund, 1967-1970 (Box 162, Folder 17)
    - Welfare Fund: Publications, 1966-1968 (Box 162, Folder 18)
    - Yeshiva University: "Academic Excellence…for the Education of the Ghetto Child", undated (Box 162, Folder 19)
  - Subseries III:J: Alan B. Lubin
    - Bushwick High School, 1971-1978 (Box 163, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence (District 32), 1974 (Box 163, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence (District 32), 1975 (Box 163, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence (District 32), 1976 (Box 163, Folder 4)
    - Intermediate School 111, 1969-1978 (Box 163, Folder 5)
    - Intermediate School 291, 1976 (Box 163, Folder 6)
    - Public School 45, 1975-1978 (Box 163, Folder 7)
    - Public School 75, 1975-1978 (Box 163, Folder 8)
    - Public School 86, 1975-1977 (Box 163, Folder 9)
    - Public School 106, 1975-1978 (Box 163, Folder 10)
    - Public School 113, 1973-1978 (Box 163, Folder 11)
    - Public School 116, 1976-1978 (Box 163, Folder 12)
    - Public School 123, 1971-1978 (Box 163, Folder 13)
    - Public School 145, 1971-1978 (Box 163, Folder 14)
    - Public School 151, 1975-1978 (Box 163, Folder 15)
    - Public School 162, 1970-1978 (Box 163, Folder 16)
    - Public School 274, 1972-1978 (Box 163, Folder 17)
    - Public School 291, 1974-1978 (Box 163, Folder 18)
    - Public School 296, 1976-1978 (Box 163, Folder 19)
    - Public School 299, 1975-1978 (Box 163, Folder 20)
    - Public School 377, 1974-1978 (Box 163, Folder 21)
    - Public School 383, 1977-1978 (Box 163, Folder 22)
    - Public School 384, 1974-1978 (Box 163, Folder 23)
  - Subseries III:K: Tom Pappas
    - Correspondence, Sep 1975 (Box 164, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, Oct 1975 (Box 164, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, Nov 1975 (Box 164, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, Dec 1975 (Box 164, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, Jan 1976 (Box 164, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, Feb 1976 (Box 164, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, Mar 1976 (Box 164, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, Apr 1976 (Box 164, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, May 1976 (Box 164, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, Jun 1976 (Box 164, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, Jul 1976-Aug 1976 (Box 164, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, Sep 1976 (Box 164, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, Oct 1976 (Box 164, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, Nov 1976 (Box 164, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, Dec 1976 (Box 164, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, Jan 1977 (Box 164, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, Feb 1977-Jul 1977 (Box 164, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, Oct 1977 (Box 164, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, Jan 1978 (Box 164, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, Feb 1978 (Box 164, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, Mar 1978 (Box 164, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, Apr 1978 (Box 164, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, May 1978 (Box 164, Folder 23)
    - Walt, Gerald: Correspondence and Memos, 1978 (Box 164, Folder 24)
    - Walt, Gerald: Correspondence and Memos, 1978 (Box 164, Folder 25)
  - Subseries III:L: Neil Rosenfield
    - Action Committee against Pataki Budget Cuts, 1998 (Box 165, Folder 1)
    - AFT-NEA Merger, 1998 (Box 165, Folder 2)
    - Asbestos in Schools, 1994-1998 (Box 165, Folder 3)
    - Asthma, 1991-1998 (Box 165, Folder 4)
    - Attendance Teacher Chapter Leader: At Risk Youth, 1997 (Box 165, Folder 5)
    - Board of Education of the City of New York: Teacher's Choice Instructional Supplies Program, 1986-1993 (Box 165, Folder 6)
    - Budget, 1999 (Box 165, Folder 7)
    - Budget, Jun 22, 1905 (Box 165, Folder 8)
    - Budget Cuts Campaign, 1990-1992 (Box 165, Folder 9)
    - Charter: NYC Revision, 1999 (Box 165, Folder 10)
    - City Council, 1995 (Box 165, Folder 11)
    - City Council, 1996 (Box 165, Folder 12)
    - Class Size: Arbitrations, 1996 (Box 165, Folder 13)
    - Contract Negotiations, 1995-1996 (Box 165, Folder 14)
    - Contract Survey, 1990 (Box 165, Folder 15)
    - Dropouts, 1985-1987 (Box 165, Folder 16)
    - Federation of Nurses: Visiting Nurses, 1989 (Box 165, Folder 17)
    - New York City Council: Lobbying, 1996 (Box 165, Folder 18)
    - PS 48x: Air Quality, 1996 (Box 165, Folder 19)
    - Shanker, Albert: Biographical Information, 1962-1996 (Box 165, Folder 20)
    - Shanker, Albert: Oral History Transcript, 1985 (Box 165, Folder 21)
    - School Budget, 1996-1998 (Box 165, Folder 22)
    - Student Mobility, 1999 (Box 165, Folder 23)
    - Substitute Vocational Assistant, 1987-1990 (Box 165, Folder 24)
    - Taxi Drivers and Allied Workers Union, Local 3036 Service Employees International Union, AFL-CIO, 1987 (Box 165, Folder 25)
    - Teacher Centers Consortium, 1993-2000 (Box 166, Folder 1)
    - Teacher Discipline, 1988-1994, 1997-2000 (Box 166, Folder 2)
    - Teacher Line, 1988-2000 (Box 166, Folder 3)
    - Teacher Training, 1978, 1986-2000 (Box 166, Folder 4)
    - Temporary Per Diem, 1989-1991 (Box 166, Folder 5)
    - Title I, 1986-1996 (Box 166, Folder 6)
    - Title I: Program, 1985 (Box 166, Folder 7)
    - Values Education, 1986, 1989 (Box 166, Folder 8)